allexamreview.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy ~ ALL EXAM REVIEW ADDA

###  At allexamreview.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by 

###  At allexamreview.com and how we use it.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.alleamreview.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.allexamreview.com does not use cookies.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.allexamreview.com.  
→ Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to www.allexamreview.com and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Opt out of the Dart Cookie")

Our Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......

  * Bidvertiser
  * Revcontent
  * Revenuhits  
  * Chitica 

_While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and  hyper-linked resource is maintained here: _[ _Privacy Policies_](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policies) _._

_You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of_

###  www.allexamreview.com _._

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.allexamreview.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

www.allexamreview.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Third Party Privacy Policies

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.www.allexamreview.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: [Privacy Policy Links](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policy-links "Privacy Policy Links").

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies)

Children's Information  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. www.allexamreview.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes thatwww.allexamreview.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

On-line Privacy Policy Only  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected off-line or via channels other than this website.

Consent  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

Update  

**This privacy policy is subjected to change without notice and was last updated on **May 15th, 2017.****
